Guide to the Stanford University Architectural Collection SC1043
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University architectural collection
1889-2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University
SC1043
2606 item(s)
The materials consist of architectural drawings of Stanford University buildings and grounds.
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of architectural drawings of Stanford University buildings and grounds.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by building.
Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge.; Church, Thomas Dolliver; Clark, Arthur Bridgman; Warnecke and Associates.; Stanford University; Church, Thomas Dolliver.; Mullgardt, Louis Christian; Stanford University -- General subdivision--Buildings.;; Bakewell and Brown; John Carl Warnecke and Associates.
- Architectural drawings
  - Inner Quad Courtyard, 1978; 01-005 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Scope and Contents note
    Artist: H. Schultz
    Description:
    # of Drawings: 1
  - Inner Quad Courtyard, 1984-85; 01-005 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Architect: Anthony M. Guzzardo
    Description: Planting Plan, Stanford Inner Quad; with planting notes and plant list
    Format: print
  - Administration, 1889; 01-010 (Box A1)
    Architect: Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge; Charles Austin
    Description: LSJU-buildings A.B.C.D.E.F.G.H.I.J.K.L. Elevations, door and window details for inner quad buildings and arcades.
    Format: microfilm reproductions
    # of Drawings: 11
  - Administration building and assembly hall, 1899; 01-120 / 01-160 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Architect: Schulze, Henry A.
    Description: North elevation. Labelled by Architect “Natural Sciences Building” but also has title “Administration Bldg and Assembly Hall reversed”
    Format: Blueprint (printed in reverse ?)
  - Political Science, 01-160 (Box A1)
    Description: Existing Law School and Library Building floor plans
    Format: photostatic copies mounted on board
    # of Drawings: 5
  - History Corner, 1976-05-11; 01-200 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Architect: Stone, Marroccini and Patterson
    Artist: H. Shultz (no. 12 only)
    Description: Reconstruction drawings; Planners: Esherick, Homsey, Dodge and Davis; Struc. Eng: Rutherford and Chekene; Mech and Elec: Ayres and Hayakawa; landscape: Richard A. Vignolo
    # of Drawings: 12
  - History Corner, 1976 Feb 10; 01-200 (Box C1)
    Architect: Stone, Marraccini and Patterson
    Description: Reconstruction Project 740 - 3 offices on second floor and 1 office in basement
    Format: diazo ?
    # of Drawings: 4
  - History Corner, 1976 Apr 1; 01-200 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Architect: Stone, Marraccini and Patterson; Esherick
    Description: History corner reconstruction - project 740--floor plans, sections, elevations
    # of Drawings: 9
  - History Corner, 1976 Sep 1; 01-200 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Description: History corner reconstruction - project 740--Design Development Drawings - architectural, structural, landscaping, mechanical, plumbing, electrical
    Format: diazo ?; bound together
    # of Drawings: 69
  - History Corner, 1977 May 1; 01-200 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Description: History corner reconstruction - project 740--architectural, landscape, structural, mechanical, plumbing, electrical
    # of Drawings: 117
  - History Corner, circa 1898; 01-200 (Box C1)
    Architect: Hodges, Chas. E.
    Description: South elevation
    Format: Blueprint
  - Civil, Mechanical and Electrical Engineering, circa 1900; 01-260 (Box D1)
    Architect: Hodges, Chas. Ed.
    Description: South elevation; scale 8 ft. to an inch
    Format: blueprint; in mylar
  - Biology Library (Jordan Hall), 1956 Apr 2; 01-420 (Box D1)
    Architect: Spencer, Eldridge T.
    Description: Biology Library, Jordan Hall, Floor Plan (showing new lighting fixtures - All-Brite 40195)
    Format: diazo?
  - Memorial Church, 1898; 01-500 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Architect: Day, Clinton
    Description: Memorial Chapel Plans. Principal [floor] plan, 1/8” scale. n.d. (ca. 1898?)
    Format: blueprint
  - Memorial Church, 1908; 01-500 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Architect: Ward and Blohme
    Artist: Hughson Hawley
    Description: Artist’s rendering of exterior facade, showing new steeple--[possibly a post-quake repair submission]--
    Format: pencil and watercolor; matted, with mylar face sheet
  - Memorial Church, 1911; 01-500
    Description: Copies of drawings, 1911
    Format: copies
    # of Drawings: 6
  - Memorial Church, 1948 Nov 15; 01-500 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Architect: Planning Office
    Description: Preliminary Alterations to Vestry
    Format: blue-line print
  - Memorial Church, 1954; 01-500 (Box C1)
    Description: Proposed Memorial Church Addition
    Format: ink on tracing paper with film overlay pasted on
  - Memorial Church, 1992; 01-500 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Artist: Fredell, Gail
    Description: Seating Plans A and B; Altar Table; Chair (4 items)--
    # of Drawings: 7
  - Memorial Church, 1991; 01-500 (Box map case Na6-7)
    Architect: Hardy Holzman Pfeiffer Associates
    Description: Memorial Church Structural Strengthening; Stanford project no. 6037
  - Memorial Church, 1912; 01-500 (Box D1)
    Description: 1/8 inch scale drawings of tower roof. Drawing no. 45, Aug. 23, 1912
  - Quad (entire), undated; 01-xxx (Box D1)
    Description: [Footprint of entire quad with building numbers; post ‘06 - no arcade behind Church - but 01-260 is labeled eng. corner not language corner]
    Format: blue line print ?
  - Balustrade, 2001; 01-xxx (Box map case Na6-7)
    Description: Full scale drawing of main Quad balustrade baluster (2cc), 2001 and 1 drawing of top rail stones
    # of Drawings: 3
  - Original Post Office, 02-001 (Box flat box B)
    Description: Original Post Office - 11/91 drawing not found in box
  - Post Office, 1900; 02-001 (Box C1)
    Architect: Hodges, Charles E.
    Description: Post Office Building for LSJU - floor plans, details of truss, roof plan
    Format: blueprints
  - Post Office, 1914-04-07; 02-001 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Bakewell and Brown
    Description: Post Office--LSJU
  - Haas Center for Public Service, 1991; 02-091 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: William Turnbull Associates
    Description: Elevations and mechanical plan
  - Bookstore - Old Union - Dinkelspiel - Tresidder, 1968 Oct 25; 02-000 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: S.U. Planning Office
    Description: no title; possibly showing some proposed buildings behind bookstore
    Format: pencil and ink on papers
    Status: Proposed
  - Bookstore, 1960-01-26; 02-010 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: LR
    Description: Bookstore and Post Office Lease Lines from Brian Survey--(stored as Q2-1)
  - Bookstore, 02-010 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Stanford University--Bookstore Expansion, schemes A-F
    # of Drawings: 10
  - Bookstore, March and May 1976; 02-010 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Warnecke and Associates
    Description: Bookstore expansion
    # of Drawings: 18
  - Bookstore, 1969-09-29; 02-010 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Keller and Daseking
    Description: Bookstore Arcade Enclosure
    # of Drawings: 2
  - Bookstore, circa 1976; 02-010 (Box B1)
    Description: Time Line for Phased v. Conventional Construction, Bookstore Expansion
    Format: 1 drawing, 1 film
  - CERAS, 1970-01-20; 02-020 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Skidmore, Owings and Merrill
    Description: Center for Research and Development in Teaching (CERAS)
  - Crown Quadrangle-Law School, 1957-11-24; 02-050 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: New Law School Facilities (includes Kresge)
  - Crown Quadrangle-Law School, 1975; 02-050 (Box C1)
    Description: Preliminary Copy Law School Seating Charts
    Format: Ink on paper
  - Serra House, 1923; 02-930 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Clark, A. B. and Clark, B. M.
    Description: Residence for David Starr Jordan, Stanford University, Calif. Elevations and floor plans
    Format: pencil on tissue
    # of Drawings: 20
  - Haas Center for Public Service, 1991-1992; 02-091 (Box Basement MC)
    Description: Site plan, planting plan, and elevations
    Format: Color copies mounted on board
  - Haas Center for Public Service, 1991-1992; 02-091 (Box C1)
    Description: East elevation (reproduction of sheet A3.1) - line negative and print
  - Dean of Chapel Home, 02-135 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Proposed semi-detached houses (LSJU); could also be considered in Quad 11--[5/95 - could not find in either Q2 or Q11 drawer]
  - Music, 1978; 02-200 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Music Building
  - Braun Music Center, Sept. 1981; 02-210 (Box C1)
    Architect: Marquis Associates
    Description: Set of 128 drawings (architectural, structural, mechanical, plumbing, electrical)
    # of Drawings: 128
  - Braun Music Center, 1980-82; 02-210 (Box Basement MC)
    Description: Site plan 1980 (rolled, top of MC Se); construction drawings for cabinetry and HVAC, 1982 (MC Se6); floor plans, landscaping 1981 (MC Se7)
    # of Drawings: 150
  - Tresidder Memorial Union, 1956-06-20; 02-300 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Preliminary, Pavilion Interior, Tresidder Memorial
  - Tresidder Memorial Union, 02-300 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Student Activities Center
  - Tresidder Memorial Union, 02-300 (Box A1)
    Architect: Spencer and Lee
    Description: South Court Tresidder Memorial Union, artist’s rendering of exterior
    Format: photographic
  - Mechanical Engineering/Center for Design Research/Civil Eng, 1962-03-21; 02-520, 02-530 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Roseck, K.A. and Dvorak, U.A.
    Description: Thermal Energy Conversion Lab (corner of Panama and Duena Sts)--”Building Locations for Oxygen Storage Site Determination”
  - Mechanical Engineering/Center for Design Research/Civil Eng, 1965 Aug 27; 02-530, 02-540 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Kump (Ernest J.) Associates
    Description: Design Institute for Environmental Science
  - Faculty Club, 1963-05-07; 02-350 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Page, Edward B.
    Description: Faculty Club - Stanford University
  - Mechanical Engineering/Center for Design Research/Civil Eng, 02-530, 02-540 (Box C1)
    Description: Civil, Mechanical and Electrical Engineering Building. Attic and Roof Plan.
    Format: blueline with pencil notes
    - Mechanical Engineering/Center for Design Research/Civil Eng, 1967 Aug 31; 02-530, 02-540 (Box map case Na8-10)
      Description: Site Development 530/540, New Facilities--[2 sets of copies w/6 and 6 drawings]
  - Mechanical Engineering/Center for Design Research/Civil Eng, 1967 Sep 22; 02-530, 02-540 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Engineering Building 530/540 Site Plan
  - Mechanical Engineering/Center for Design Research/Civil Eng, 1968 Aug 26; 02-530, 02-540 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Remodel Building 530/540 Site, Floor, and Section Plans--[6 sets of copies w/4, 4, 4, 5, 6, or 6 drawings] [3 loose drawings - entrance, graphic analysis of space needs (2 c.)]
  - Mechanical Engineering/Center for Design Research/Civil Eng, 1968 Sep 20; 02-530, 02-540 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Remodelling of Engineering Buildings 530/540--[2 sets of copies w/14 or 18 drawings] [1 set of 11 drawings]
  - Mechanical Engineering/Center for Design Research/Civil Eng, 02-540 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Aerodynamic Laboratory (razed)
    Status: Razed
  - Student Services Building (Old union), 02-580 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Johns, H.W.
    Description: Acoustical treatment (Stanford Union)
  - Student Services Building (Old Union), 02-580 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Mancrum and Otter
    Description: Stanford Union kitchen
  - Student Services Building (Old Union), 02-580 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Office for New Union Building--4/95 not in drawer
  - Old Union - Arcade, 02-580 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Artist: unknown
    Description: pencil sketch of arcade; on tissue; scale 1/4” = 1 ft.--33 in x 20 in--[found among prints, unprocessed; transferred to arch draw]
    Format: sketch
  - Old Union, 21-May; 02-580 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Main entrance of front facade
    Format: pencil on paper
  - Nitery, 02-590 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Revised Plan of Stanford Union Building, Men’s Building
  - Men’s Clubhouse, 1968; 02-590 (Box C1)
    Architect: S.U. Physical Plant Dept.
    Description: Proposed exterior stairway.
    Format: blueline prints
  - Mechanical Engineering (Old Corporation Yard), 1936 April 9; 02-610 (Box B1)
    Description: Old Corporation Yard Roofing Materials Schematic. Although dated the same, there are differences in placement of buildings. Paper copy shows service station.
    Format: ink on linen with watercolor; ink on paper
  - Forge and Foundry Shop, 02-610 (Box A1)
    Description: Forge and Foundry Shops, Fig. 1 Present Arrangement and Fig. 2 Proposed Arrangement
  - News and Publications, 02-635 (Box C1)
    Description: Press Building. Artist’s rendering of courtyard and exterior.
    Format: Watercolor, pen and ink on paper
  - News and Publications, 1963 Mar 21; 02-635 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Press (News and Publications)
  - Alpha Sigma Phi (razed 1972), 1964 Mar 18; 02-912 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: JR
    Description: Conversion of Alpha Sigma Phi house for Psychology Animal Labs (razed 1972)
  - Storey House, 1980 Sep 10; 02-921 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Rupp, Sigrid Lorenzen
    Description: Storey House Reconstruction
  - Serra House, 1959 Nov 5; 02-930 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Stanford Planning Office
    Description: Tree and ditch location plan for Serra House parking survey--(This plan is for pre-1978 Serra House which would have been located in Q14)
  - Lasuen Mall, 1964; 02-xxx (Box A1)
    Architect: Nelson,Oscar F. Jr.
    Description: Proposed plan for improvement of Lasuen Mall [from Campus Drive to Dinkelspiel] --(stored at Q2 but could also be Q5)
    Format: ink on paper
  - Stanford Band Stand, 1916; 02-xxx (Box C1)
    Description: Band Stand for Leland Stanford Jr. University. Plans, elevations, and sections.
  - Stanford Band Stand, 1916; 02-xxx (Box B1)
    Description: Section on Center Line Showing Radius of Curve; Front Elevation; Side Elevation and Section on Center Line
    Format: pencil on paper (encapsulated)
  - Stanford Band Stand, 1916 (Nov. - Dec.); 02-xxx (Box B1)
    Description: Band Stand for Stanford Univ.: elevations, sections, foundation plans
  - Engineering Research Labs, 1942 Aug 22; 02-xxx (Box B1)
    Description: [Engineering Research Labs] floor plan for addition to existing building. [location and quad is uncertain]
  - Library Quad, 1967 Dec 5; 03-000 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Architect: Church, Thomas
    Artist: Lawrence G. Brian and Co., civil engineers
    Description: Portion of Library Quad Master Plan from and of Meyer Library to Campus Drive proposed including parking lot ‘J’--[needs conservation work - cleaning and repair]
    Format: watercolor and ink over printed drawing
  - Thomas Welton Stanford Picture Gallery, 1916; 03-001 (Box D1)
    Description: Plans, elevations, details, sections
    Format: printed from microfiche or microfilm
  - Thomas Welton Stanford Picture Gallery, 1946; 03-001 (Box D1)
    Architect: S. U. Planning Department
    Description: Cross sections, elevation
  - Thomas Welton Stanford Picture Gallery, 1916; 03-001 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Plans, elevations, details,
    Format: brown-toned print
  - Thomas Welton Stanford Picture Gallery, 1916; 03-001 (Box not specified)
    Description: Thomas W. Stanford Picture Gallery, Bakewell and Brown, architects, 1916 - 16 items,
    # of Drawings: 16
  - Thomas Welton Stanford Art Gallery, 1946; 03-001 (Box D1)
    Architect: Eldridge T. Spencer
    Description: Window details
  - Cummings Art Building, 1964 Sep 17; 03-010 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Art Building stages 1 and 2
  - Cummings Art Building, 1965 Mar 23; 03-010 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Art Building Diagrammatic Floor Plans
  - Cummings Art Building, 1966 Jan 6; 03-010 (Box C1)
    Artist: O. Dahlstrand
    Description: Proposed Art Building. Sketch of exterior.
    Format: reproduction
  - Cummings Art Building, 1966 Jan 6; 03-010 (Box B1)
    Description: Sketches for proposed Art Building: 3 exteriors, 1 interior
  - Cummings Art Building, 1966 Jan 16; 03-010 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Art Building Stanford University
  - Cummings Art Building, 1968; 03-010 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Architect: unknown
    Description: [Planting scheme for art building; master card file no. 991; reviewed by Fac. Adv. Comm. Dec. 20, 1968; includes photo of sculpture]
    Format: diazo print with colored pencil details; in mylar
  - Dohrmann Grove, 1970 Oct 20; 03-005 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Architect: Ralfs, D.J.
    Artist: JR
    Description: Dohrmann Memorial Planting Plan
  - Hoover Library, Jan. 1926; 03-110 (Box A1)
    Description: The Hoover LIbrary. Elevation
  - Hoover Tower, 1939; 03-100 (Box A1)
    Architect: [Bakewell and Brown ?]
    Description: [Hoover Library and Archives]. Floor plans.
    # of Drawings: 8
  - Hoover Tower, 1926-1930; 03-100 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Hoover Library (LSJU)
  - Hoover Tower, 1964 Sep 6; 03-100 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Architect: Church, Thomas D. and Associates
    Artist: June Meehan, Jack Stafford
    Description: Hoover Tower Area - suggestons of relationships of future buildings
  - Hoover Tower, 1963 Dec 16; 03-100 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Architect: Stanford University Planning Office
    Description: Hoover Institute - proposed renovations
  - Hoover Tower, 1964 Apr 22; 03-100 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Preliminary plans - Hoover Institute Renovation
  - Hoover Tower, 1965 Sep 9; 03-100 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Hoover Tower Grille Work
  - Hoover Tower, 1964 Nov 19; 03-100 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Architect: Luckman Assoc.
    Description: Sketch of Hoover Institution Buildings
  - Hoover Tower, 03-100 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Drawings - Hoover Institution Building, Hoover Tower
  - Herbert Hoover Memorial Building, 1916-12-05; 03-120 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Plan of Proposed Buildings for the LSJU (in proposed new quad) (includes Green Library)
  - Herbert Hoover Memorial Building, 30-Aug; 03-120 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Main Quadrangle and Proposed Second Quad
  - Herbert Hoover Memorial Building, 03-120 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Preliminary Sketch for Proposed Food Research and Hoover Library Buildings at LSJU--(stored as Q3 but could also be Q6)
  - Herbert Hoover Memorial Building, 1948; 03-120 (Box B1)
    Architect: Spencer, Eldridge ?
    Description: Study for Library Quad - Extensions to Hoover Library----
    Format: photostat
  - Herbert Hoover Memorial Building, 03-120 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Second Quadrangle - Stanford University (with Green Library)
  - Library, 1916; 03-200 (Box B1)
    Description: Library Building for Leland Stanford Jr. University. Elevations and sections.
  - Library, 1916; 03-200 (Box C1)
    Description: Library Building for Leland Stanford Jr. University. Floor Plans.
  - Library, 1917; 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Front elevation drawing
    Format: ink on paper, with colored washes; framed
  - Library, 1917; 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Main Library plans: set of 12 dated 2/15/17 - 4/16/17; set of 12 dated 2/1/17; one basement plan dated January 1917; two misc. drawings (not BandB)
    # of Drawings: 27
  - Library, 1917; 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Green Library - Heating, Wiring and Plumbing Plan
  - Library, circa 1960; 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Architect: Planning Department
    Description: Proposed alterations to the main floor of the Stanford Library.--[drawing is 1957, but not sure of date of notations]
    Format: paper copy with pencil and ink notations
  - Library, 1968; 03-200 (Box D1)
    Architect: Hellmuth, Obata and Kassabaum, Inc.
    Description: Stanford University, Main Library Development Master Plan
  - Library, 1969 Dec 31; 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Architect: Hellmuth, Obata and Kassabaum
    Description: Main Library Development, New Building Plans. Levels 1-5 and Elevations--Elec Eng: Aures, Cohen and Hayakawa
  - Library, 1969; 03-210 (Box D1)
    Architect: Hellmuth Obata and Kassabaum
    Description: Floor plans for levels 1 through 5; mostly for new east wing but also includes some plans for existing library. Two copies of each, some with notes.
  - Library, 1974; 03-200 (Box A1)
    Description: Green Library Floor Plans [West Wing]
    Format: stats for printing
  - Library, 1969 Dec 31; 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Main Library Development - New Building--Struc Eng: Pregnoff and Matheu
  - Library, 1970; 03-210 (Box A1)
    Description: Green Library East Reference and Reading Rooms--[one bears Planning Office stamp dated Nov. 4, 1970 suggesting these are from an earlier proposal]
    Format: illustrations, matted
  - Cecil H. Green Library, 1985 Feb 4; 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Stanford University - Main Library Development--Bender Room Remodel
  - Cecil H. Green Library, 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Main Library Development - Utility Realignment
  - Proposed Second Quadrangle (Library and others), circa 1917; 03-200 (Box C1)
    Description: Proposal for University Library and 2nd Quadrangle Expansion. presentation drawing.
    Format: graphite and colored pencil on tissue, encapsulated
  - Cecil H. Green Library, 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Green Library - Riser Diagram Heating, Wiring and Plumbing Plan
  - Cecil H. Green Library, 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Green Library
    Format: encapsulated and matted
  - Cecil H. Green Library, 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Alterations to Basement - Stanford University Library--(original listing has ? for quad no. suggesting this might be the library in the Quad)
  - Cecil H. Green Library, West Wing, 1995; 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Architect: [Bakewell and Brown]
    Description: Historic American Buildings Survey Drawings, CA-2613. 40 drawings, 1 cover sheet. Includes reproductions of some original Bakewell and Brown drawings.
    Format: on vellum
    # of Drawings: 41
  - Cecil H. Green Library, West Wing, 1995; 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Format: on mylar
  - Cecil H. Green Library, West Wing, 1998 Oct 8; 03-200 (Box D1)
    Architect: Clay, Ed
    Description: Plans for the Rotunda Table
    Format: photocopy?
  - Cecil H. Green Library, West Wing, 1995; 03-200 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Architect: Brayton and Hughes
    Description: Six plans at time of renovation of West Wing: 1st floor elevation, office 101B, Bender Room (3 items), elevation for Barchas and Field room
  - Law Group, 1937-05-14; 03-xxx (Box C1)
    Description: Preliminary Studies for Law Group (Quad design including Green Library, art gallery, education building, law group)
  - Law Group, 1938 Apr 10; 03-xxx (Box B1)
    Description: Preliminary Study for Law Building. Elevations and Floor Plan. (part of Quad design including Green Library, art gallery, education building, law group)
    Format: ink and pencil on tissue (in mylar)
  - Law Group, 1938 Apr 20; 03-xxx (Box B1)
    Description: Preliminary Studies for Law Group. First Floor Plan. (part of Quad design including Green Library, art gallery, education building, law group)
    Format: tissue, in mylar